{
  "nodes": {
    "0": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_over_35_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 1,
      "right": 14,
      "samples": 20,
      "question": "Is the actor over 35 years old",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "1": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_father_famous_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 2,
      "right": 9,
      "samples": 9,
      "question": "Is your actor's Father famous ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "2": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "has_kids_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 3,
      "right": 8,
      "samples": 5,
      "question": "Does your actor have kids ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "3": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "nationality_indian_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 4,
      "right": 5,
      "samples": 4,
      "question": "Is your actor indian ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "4": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Jacqueline Fernandez",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "5": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_male_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 6,
      "right": 7,
      "samples": 3,
      "question": "Is the actor male or Female",
      "left_label": "Female",
      "right_label": "Male"
    },
    "6": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Taapsee Pannu",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "7": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Ranveer Singh",
      "samples": 2
    },
    "8": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Anushka Sharma",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "9": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "film_producer_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 10,
      "right": 11,
      "samples": 4,
      "question": "Is you actor a film producer as well ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "10": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Alia Bhatt",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "11": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_comedy_actor_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 12,
      "right": 13,
      "samples": 3,
      "question": "Is he comedy actor ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "12": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Ranbir Kapoor",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "13": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Ayushmann Khurrana",
      "samples": 2
    },
    "14": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_father_famous_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 15,
      "right": 22,
      "samples": 11,
      "question": "Is your actor's Father famous ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "15": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_male_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 16,
      "right": 19,
      "samples": 5,
      "question": "Is the actor male or Female",
      "left_label": "Female",
      "right_label": "Male"
    },
    "16": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "has_kids_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 17,
      "right": 18,
      "samples": 3,
      "question": "Does your actor have kids ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "17": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Katrina Kaif",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "18": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Rani Mukerji",
      "samples": 2
    },
    "19": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_romance_actor_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 20,
      "right": 21,
      "samples": 2,
      "question": "Is he romance actor ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "20": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Akshay Kumar",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "21": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Shah Rukh Khan",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "22": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "film_producer_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 23,
      "right": 28,
      "samples": 6,
      "question": "Is you actor a film producer as well ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "23": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_romance_actor_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 24,
      "right": 25,
      "samples": 3,
      "question": "Is he romance actor ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "24": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Priyanka Chopra",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "25": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "has_kids_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 26,
      "right": 27,
      "samples": 2,
      "question": "Does your actor have kids ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "26": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Deepika Padukone",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "27": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Kareena Kapoor",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "28": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "has_kids_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 29,
      "right": 32,
      "samples": 3,
      "question": "Does your actor have kids ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "29": {
      "type": "internal",
      "feature": "is_muslim_n",
      "threshold": 0.5,
      "left": 30,
      "right": 31,
      "samples": 2,
      "question": "Is your actor Muslim ?",
      "left_label": "No",
      "right_label": "Yes"
    },
    "30": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Hrithik Roshan",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "31": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Salman Khan",
      "samples": 1
    },
    "32": {
      "type": "leaf",
      "predicted_class": "Aamir Khan",
      "samples": 1
    }
  },
  "root": 0,
  "feature_names": [
    "is_male_n",
    "is_indian_n",
    "is_over_35_n",
    "worked_in_movies_n",
    "is_action_actor_n",
    "is_romance_actor_n",
    "is_comedy_actor_n",
    "is_drama_actor_n",
    "is_muslim_n",
    "is_married_n",
    "has_kids_n",
    "happy_new_year_movie_n",
    "nationality_indian_n",
    "film_producer_n",
    "is_father_famous_n"
  ],
  "class_names": [
    "Aamir Khan",
    "Akshay Kumar",
    "Alia Bhatt",
    "Anushka Sharma",
    "Ayushmann Khurrana",
    "Deepika Padukone",
    "Hrithik Roshan",
    "Jacqueline Fernandez",
    "Kareena Kapoor",
    "Katrina Kaif",
    "Priyanka Chopra",
    "Ranbir Kapoor",
    "Rani Mukerji",
    "Ranveer Singh",
    "Salman Khan",
    "Shah Rukh Khan",
    "Taapsee Pannu",
    "Varun Dhawan",
    "Vicky Kaushal",
    "Vidya Balan"
  ]
}